Jensen, Vernon Collection of International Longshoremen's Association's and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen's Materials 5487
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.74-126 (1974: July 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.74-127 (1974: July 3)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.74-128 (1974: July 5)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.74-129 (1974: July 8)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.74-130 (1974: July 9)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.74-131 (1974: July 10)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.74-132 (1974: July 11)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.74-133 (1974: July 12)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.74-134 (1974: July 15)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.74-135 (1974: July 16)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.74-136 (1974: July 17)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.74-137 (1974: July 18)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.74-138 (1974: July 19)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.74-139 (1974: July 22)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.74-140 (1974: July 23)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.74-141 (1974: July 24)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.74-142 (1974: July 25)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.74-143 (1974: July 26)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.74-144 (1974: July 29)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.74-145 (1974: July 30)
  - Item 22: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.74-146 (1974: July 31)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.74-147 (1974: Aug. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.74-148 (1974: Aug. 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.74-149 (1974: Aug. 5)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.74-150 (1974: Aug. 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.74-151 (1974: Aug. 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.74-152 (1974: Aug. 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.74-153 (1974: Aug. 9)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.74-154 (1974: Aug. 12)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.74-155 (1974: Aug. 13)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.74-156 (1974: Aug. 14)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.74-157 (1974: Aug. 15)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.74-158 (1974: Aug. 16)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.74-159 (1974: Aug. 19)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.74-160 (1974: Aug. 20)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.74-161 (1974: Aug. 21)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.74-162 (1974: Aug. 22)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.74-163 (1974: Aug. 23)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.74-164 (1974: Aug. 26)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.74-165 (1974: Aug. 27)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.74-166 (1974: Aug. 28)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.74-167 (1974: Aug. 29)
  - Item 22: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.74-168 (1974: Aug. 30)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.74-169 (1974: Sep. 3)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.74-170 (1974: Sep. 4)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.74-171 (1974: Sep. 5)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.74-172 (1974: Sep. 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.74-173 (1974: Sep. 9)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.74-174 (1974: Sep. 10)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.74-175 (1974: Sep. 11)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.74-176 (1974: Sep. 12)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.74-177 (1974: Sep. 13)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.74-178 (1974: Sep. 16)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.74-179 (1974: Sep. 17)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.74-180 (1974: Sep. 18)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.74-181 (1974: Sep. 19)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.74-182 (1974: Sep. 20)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.74-183 (1974: Sep. 23)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.74-184 (1974: Sep. 24)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.74-185 (1974: Sep. 25)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.74-186 (1974: Sep. 26)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.74-187 (1974: Sep. 27)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.74-188 (1974: Sep. 30)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.74-189 (1974: Oct. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.74-190 (1974: Oct. 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.74-191 (1974: Oct. 3)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.74-192 (1974: Oct. 4)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.74-193 (1974: Oct. 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.74-194 (1974: Oct. 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.74-195 (1974: Oct. 9)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.74-196 (1974: Oct. 10)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.74-197 (1974: Oct. 11)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.74-198 (1974: Oct. 15)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.74-199 (1974: Oct. 16)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.74-200 (1974: Oct. 17)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.74-201 (1974: Oct. 18)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.74-202 (1974: Oct. 21)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.74-203 (1974: Oct. 22)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.74-204 (1974: Oct. 23)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.74-205 (1974: Oct. 24)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.74-206 (1974: Oct. 25)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.74-207 (1974: Oct. 29)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.74-208 (1974: Oct. 30)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.74-209 (1974: Oct. 31)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.74-210 (1974: Nov. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.74-211 (1974: Nov. 4)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.74-212 (1974: Nov. 6)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.74-213 (1974: Nov. 7)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.74-214 (1974: Nov. 8)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.74-215 (1974: Nov. 12)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.74-216 (1974: Nov. 13)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.74-217 (1974: Nov. 14)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.74-218 (1974: Nov. 15)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.74-219 (1974: Nov. 18)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.74-220 (1974: Nov. 19)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.74-221 (1974: Nov. 20)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.74-222 (1974: Nov. 21)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.74-223 (1974: Nov. 22)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.74-224 (1974: Nov. 25)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.74-225 (1974: Nov. 26)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.74-226 (1974: Nov. 27)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.74-227 (1974: Dec. 2)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.74-228 (1974: Dec. 3)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.74-229 (1974: Dec. 4)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.74-230 (1974: Dec. 5)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.74-231 (1974: Dec. 6)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.74-232 (1974: Dec. 9)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.74-233 (1974: Dec. 10)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.74-234 (1974: Dec. 11)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.74-235 (1974: Dec. 12)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.74-236 (1974: Dec. 13)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.74-237 (1974: Dec. 16)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.74-238 (1974: Dec. 17)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.74-239 (1974: Dec. 18)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.74-240 (1974: Dec. 19)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.74-241 (1974: Dec. 20)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.74-242 (1974: Dec. 23)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.74-243 (1974: Dec. 26)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.74-244 (1974: Dec. 27)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.74-245 (1974: Dec. 30)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.74-246 (1974: Dec. 31)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.75-1 (1975: Jan. 2)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.75-2 (1975: Jan 3)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.75-3 (1975: Jan 6)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.75-4 (1975: Jan 7)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.75-8 (1975: Jan 8)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.75-5 (1975: Jan 9)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.75-6 (1975: Jan 10)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.75-7 (1975: Jan 13)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.75-8 (1975: Jan 14)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.75-9 (1975: Jan 15)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.75-10 (1975: Jan 16)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.75-11 (1975: Jan 17)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.75-12 (1975: Jan 20)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.75-13 (1975: Jan 21)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.75-14 (1975: Jan 22)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.75-15 (1975: Jan 23)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.75-16 (1975: Jan 24)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.75-17 (1975: Jan 27)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.75-18 (1975: Jan 28)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.75-19 (1975: Jan 29)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.75-20 (1975: Jan 30)
  - Item 22: Todd Daily Maritime, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.75-21 (1975: Jan 31)
- Christian Science Monitor, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: air-Cargo industry burgeons as wide-body jets increase capacity, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Author: Frederick H. Guidy
    Notes: September 4, 1973.
  - Item 2: Air Cargo goes piggyback, too, with efficiency pulling new profits, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Notes: September 5, 1973.
  - Item 3: Airfreight slowly lifts itself off back burner, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Notes: September 6, 1973.
  - Item 4: What price peace on U. S. docks?, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Author: Ed Townsend
    Notes: April 4, 1974.
- ITF Newsletter, 1973-1975 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: ITF Newsletter, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Author: International Transport Workers' Federation (ITF)
    Notes: no.3 (1973:Mar.)
  - Item 2: ITF Newsletter, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.8 (1973:Aug.)
  - Item 3: ITF Newsletter, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.9 (1974:Sep.)
  - Item 4: ITF Newsletter, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.10 (1974:Oct.)
  - Item 5: ITF Newsletter, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.11 (1974:Nov.)
  - Item 6: ITF Newsletter, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.12 (1974:Dec.)
  - Item 7: ITF Newsletter, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.3 (1975:Mar.)
  - Item 8: ITF Newsletter, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.4 (1973:Apr.)
- Local 824 Bulletin, 1968-1975 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  International Longshoremen's Association
  - Item 1: Local 824 Bulletin, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Author: International Longshoremen's Association, Local 824
    Notes: v.3:no.4 (1968:Oct.)
  - Item 2: Local 824 Bulletin, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Notes: v.8:no.1 (1973:Mar.)
  - Item 3: Local 824 Bulletin, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Notes: v.9:no.3 (1974:Nov.)
  - Item 4: Local 824 Bulletin, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Notes: v.10:no.1 (1975:Spring)
- New York Times, 1968-1973 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Me Too' Demands Feared In Ports, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Author: George Horne
    Notes: July 4, 1968.
  - Item 2: Unsarling Port May Take Weeks, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Notes: March 2, 1969.
  - Item 3: Some Teamsters Oppose Dock Pact, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Author: The New York Times
    Notes: February 12, 1972.
  - Item 4: Dock Wages: Pay Board Seems to Have Won The Big Test, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Notes: May 14, 1972.
  - Item 5: Growth of Arbitration Appears to Point to Era of Labor Peace, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Author: Philip Shabecoff
    Notes: April 22, 1973.
- NYSA-ILA, 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  New York State Shipping Association. International Longshoremen's Association
  - Item 1: L.R.C. Report no.207, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Author: Port of New York Labor Relations Committee
    Notes: November 30, 1972.
  - Item 2: L.R.C. Report no.209, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Notes: February 8, 1973.
  - Item 3: L.R.C. Report no.210, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Notes: February 16, 1973.
  - Item 4: Prior Day Order Debits, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Author: Contract Board
    Notes: February 20, 1973.
  - Item 5: Portwide P.D.O. Hiring, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Notes: April 10, 1974.
- Bureau of National Affairs, 1971-1974 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Current Developments Section, A-12, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Author: Bureau of National Affairs
    Notes: no.139 (1971:July 20)
  - Item 2: Current Developments Section, A-4, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.167 (1974:Aug. 27)
- Miscellaneous Clippings, 1971-1974 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: News: Fact Sheet on Collective Bargaining in the Longshore Industry, 1958-70, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Author: Bureau of Labor Statistics
    Notes: USDL: 71-470 (1971:Sep. 10)
  - Item 2: Special Bulletin, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Author: Hawaii Employers Council
    Notes: no.58 (1971:Sep. 17)
  - Item 3: Containers sap St. Lawrence trade, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Author: Eric Dowd
    Notes: September 14, 1973.
  - Item 4: Ports: Mr Jones's benefit, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Author: The Economist
    Notes: August 24, 1974.
- Railroad Arbitration Board no.282 [folder 1 of 2], 1964 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Railroad Arbitration Board no.282 [folder 2 of 2], 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Reference Book Award of Arbitration Board no.282, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Reference Book Award of Arbitration Board no.282, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Author: Abritration Board no.282
  - Item 2: Daily Labor Report no.229: Arbitration Board no.282, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Author: Washington Daily Reporter System
- Due Process on the Railroads, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Due Process on the Railroads, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Author: Joseph Lazar
- Jacob Kaufman, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Logic and Meaning of Work Rules on the Railroads (Box 3, Folder 25)
    Author: Jacob J. Kaufman
  - Item 2: Logic and Meaning of Work Rules on the Railroads (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: Working Rules in the Railroad Industry, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    Notes: Reprinted from Labor Law Journal, December 1954.
  - Item 4: Working Rules in the Railroad Industry, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    Notes: Reprinted from Labor Law Journal, December 1954. Copy 2.
- Railroad Labor Relations, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Suggested Readings in Railroad Labor Relations, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1959-1964 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Carriers Section 6 Notice: National Rules Proposals, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Author: General Grievance Committee
    Notes: November 2, 1959.
  - Item 2: Carriers Section 6 Notice: National Rules Proposals, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Notes: September 7, 1960.
  - Item 3: To all engine, train and yard service employees, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Author: W. A. Harris
    Notes: July 29, 1963.
  - Item 4: To all engine, train and yard service employees, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Author: C. J. Schuler
    Notes: April 10, 1964.
- Labor Problems in the Transportation Industry, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Labor Problems of th Transportation Industry, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Author: Eli L. Oliver
    Notes: Reprinted from the symposium on Transportation: Part II. Published as the Winter, 1960, issue of Law and Contemporary Problems.
- Are Firemen Required in Diesel Locomotives, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Are Firemen Required on Diesel Locomotives?, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    Author: Norman Coates
    Notes: v.6:no.1 (1960:Spring)
- Railroad Mergers, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: The Move Toward Railroad Mergers: A Great National Problem, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    Author: Railway Labor Executives' Association
  - Item 2: The Public Interest Demands Merger (Box 3, Folder 30)
    Author: Penn-Central Merger Information Committee
  - Item 3: Facts About The Proposed Merger of the Pennsylvania and New York Central Railroads, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Railroad Poverty: Fact or Fable, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Railroad Poverty: Fact or Fable?, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    Author: American Trucking Association
- Daily Labor Report, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Daily Labor Report no.187: Statement of Legislative History Concerning Issues to be Arbitrated Under Railroad Arbitration Act, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    Notes: September 25, 1963.
- The Case for Locomotive Helpers (Firemen), 1963 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: The Case for Locomotive Helpers (Firemen), 1963 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    Author: Dick Murway; Bill Loftus
    Notes: October 18, 1963.
- Railroad Rules Dispute, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Why Congress Should Not Permit the Interstate Commerce Commission to Settle the Current Railroad Work Rules Controversy, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Item 2: Rules Dispute Ended, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    Author: The Enginemen's Press
    Notes: v.6:no.17 (1964:Apr. 24). Complete newspaper: contains other articles.
  - Item 3: Kennedy Asks ICC Power to Referee Rail Dispute in 2-Year No-Strike Plan, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    Notes: v.112:no.38,531 (1963:July 23)
  - Item 4: Chaos' Is Feared: President Warns of Economic Setback in Major Tieup, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    Author: John D. Pomfret
  - Item 5: Rail Workers Here Assail Kennedy Plan, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    Author: Peter Millones
  - Item 6: Texts of Kennedy Message to Congress on Rail Dispute and of Proposed Resolution, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 34)